<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>"I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." ― Douglas Adams</item>
        <item>"There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." ― Maya Angelou</item>
        <item>"There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." ― Ernest Hemingway</item>
        <item>"If you don't have time to read, you don't have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>"If there's a book that you want to read, but it hasn't been written yet, then you must write it." ― Toni Morrison</item>
        <item>"One day I will find the right words, and they will be simple." ― Jack Kerouac</item>
        <item>"No tears in the writer, no tears in the reader. No surprise in the writer, no surprise in the reader." ― Robert Frost</item>
        <item>"The difference between the right word and the almost right word is the difference between lightning and a lightning bug." ― Mark Twain</item>
        <item>"Writing is a socially acceptable form of schizophrenia." ― E.L. Doctorow</item>
        <item>"History will be kind to me for I intend to write it." ― Winston S. Churchill</item>
        <item>"How vain it is to sit down to write when you have not stood up to live." ― Henry David Thoreau</item>
        <item>"Start writing, no matter what. The water does not flow until the faucet is turned on." ― Louis L\'Amour</item>
        <item>"Writing starts with living." ― L.L. Barkat</item>
        <item>"I write because, if I don\'t, my characters will murder me in my sleep." ― Astrid Cruz</item>
        <item>"Write to amuse? What an appalling suggestion! I write to make people anxious and miserable and to worsen their indigestion." ― Wendy Cope</item>
        <item>"The historian records, but the novelist creates." ― E.M. Forster</item>
        <item>"A great many people have come up to me and asked how I manage to get so much work done and still keep looking so dissipated." ― Robert Benchley</item>
        <item>"The hard part is putting one word after another." ― Jo Linsdell</item>
        <item>"Writing is a lot like making soup. My subconscious cooks the idea, but I have to sit down at the computer to pour it out." ― Robin Wells</item>
        <item>"I prefer the pen. There is something elemental about the glide and flow of nib and ink on paper." ― James Robertson</item>
        <item>"There's an old rule of theater that goes, 'If there's a gun on the mantel in Act I, it must go off in Act III.' The reverse is also true." ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>"Write quickly and you will never write well; write well, and you will soon write quickly." ― Marcus Fabius Quintilianus</item>
        <item>"The awful part of the writing game is that you can never be sure the stuff is any good." ― P.G. Wodehouse</item>
        <item>"I do not wish to comment on the work; if it does not speak for itself, it is a failure." ― George Orwell</item>
        <item>"Sometimes the body gets out of bed an hour before the brain." ― Peter James West</item>
        <item>"I want to write an unreliable narrator. In fact, he’ll be so unreliable that I’m not even sure he’ll show up to narrate." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"I hope you enjoy reading my book as much as I didn’t enjoy writing it. Just kidding! I hope you don’t enjoy it at all." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"If you can listen to or read anything, but misspelled words offend you, raise your hadn." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"I want to write a book called "Conversations." Of course, it’s all talk at this point." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"The artist must manage to make posterity believe that he never existed." ― Gustave Flaubert</item>
        <item>"No iron can pierce the human heart as chillingly as a full stop placed at the right time." ― Isaac Babel</item>
        <item>"The average novel invariably reads like a detective's report. It is drab and tedious because it is never objective." ― Natsume Sōseki</item>
        <item>"Science fiction is very well suited to asking philosophical questions; questions about the nature of reality, what it means to be human, how do we know the things that we think we know." ― Ted Chiang</item>
        <item>"I know writers who use subtext, and they're all cowards." ― Garth Marenghi</item>
        <item>"You will learn more about writing from one hour of reading than you will in six hours of writing." ― John McAleer</item>
        <item>"No one writes anything worth writing, unless he writes entirely for the sake of his subject." ― Arthur Schopenhauer</item>
        <item>"Be prepared to work hard to be a writer." ― Sandra Brown</item>
        <item>"&#8230;writers are often the worst judges of what they have written." ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>Good writing is supposed to evoke sensation in the reader - not the fact that it is raining, but the feeling of being rained upon. - E. L. Doctorow</item>
        <item>I\'m writing a book. I\'ve got the page numbers done. - Steven Wright</item>
        <item>The main problem with writing in verse is, if your fourth line doesn\'t come out right, you\'ve got to throw four lines away and figure out a whole new way to attack the problem. So the mortality rate is terrific. - Dr. Seuss</item>
        <item>"Humility is an essential quality in writers who want to write well." ― Margaret Jean Langstaff</item>
        <item>"I write to escape. I haven't managed it yet, but I'm working on it" ― William Meikle</item>
        <item>"When a character comes to life, it’s like meeting a new friend for the first time." ― Lynette Mather</item>
        <item>"To be a well-favoured man is the gift of fortune; but to write and read comes by nature." ― William Shakespeare</item>
        <item>"Sure, it's simple writing for kids…just as simple as bringing them up." ― Ursula K. Le Guin</item>
        <item>"Write when you least feel like it, because that's when you write best." ― Nema Al-Araby</item>
        <item>"I wanted to write the most beautiful poem but that is impossible; the world has written its own." ― Dejan Stojanovic</item>
        <item>"Write every day. Even if it's only a letter." ― Julia Bell</item>
        <item>"I intend all my characters must escape from impossible situations; if they are not in trouble, then as a writer, I am." ― Cleveland W. Gibson</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I’ll read a book and feel it was written just for me. Then I’ll flip the book over to look at the cover to see who wrote it, only to discover that it feels like it was written for me because it was written by me." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"Literature is the art of writing something that will be read twice." ― Cyril Connolly</item>
        <item>"The purpose of writing is to hold a mirror to nature, but too much today is written from small mirrors in vanity cases." ― John Mason Brown</item>
        <item>"Many of the characters are fools and they're always playing tricks on me and treating me badly." ― Jorge Luis Borges</item>
        <item>"Life's adventures make great reading!" ― Denise Robbins</item>
        <item>"Inspiration comes and goes, creativity is the result of practice." ― Phil Cousineau</item>
        <item>"The paper is patient, but the reader is not." ― Joseph Joubert</item>
        <item>"Yes, it's hard to write, but it's harder not to." ― Carl Van Doren</item>
        <item>"Many people can and have written books, but many have nothing to say." ― Amy Rogers</item>
        <item>"I wonder what the retirement age is in the novel business. The day you die." ― Yasunari Kawabata</item>
        <item>"If the desire to write is not accompanied by actual writing, then the desire must be not to write." ― Hugh Prather</item>
        <item> "After being turned down by numerous publishers, he decided to write for posterity." ― George Ade</item>
        <item>"When a writer tries to explain too much, he's out of time before he begins." ― Isaac Bashevis Singer</item>
        <item>"As for writing, that's a cruel hard business. Unless you're very lucky it'll break your heart." ― Edward Abbey</item>
        <item>"Language imparts identity, meaning, and perspective to our human condition. Writers are either polluters or part of the cleanup." ― Mary Pipher</item>
        <item>"Writers don't write from experience, although many are hesitant to admit that they don't&#8230; If you wrote from experience, you'd get maybe one book, maybe three poems. Writers write from empathy." ― Nikki Giovanni</item>
        <item>"Do you like reading? It's the best thing that can happen to you in life. Writing has other implications." ― Manuel Rivas</item>
        <item>"I’ve always believed writing ads is the second most profitable form of writing. The first is ransom notes…" ― Phil Dusenberry</item>
        <item>"Above all things &#8212; read. Read the great stylists who cannot be copied rather than the successful writers who must not be copied." ― Ngaio Marsh</item>
        <item>"Writing is a mysterious activity." ― Susan Sontag</item>
        <item>"Writing is like life: it goes on." ― Marty Rubin</item>
        <item>"Persistence can look a lot like stupid." ― Kristen Lamb</item>
        <item>"Seeing your own name on the book cover is like hearing your book saying, "Hi. Thanks for writing me!" ― Alvi Syahrin</item>
        <item>"Get to work. Your work is to keep cranking the flywheel that turns the gears that spin the belt in the engine of belief that keeps you and your desk in midair." ― Annie Dillard</item>
        <item>"Most writing is done between the mind and the hand, not between the hand and the page." ― Janet Burroway</item>
        <item>"And so I just kept writing to myself." ― Kimberly Novosel</item>
        <item>"Words are a puzzle; put them together the right way and you get something beautiful." ― Amy Joy</item>
        <item>"The code of the coward is to run away. I know, because I wrote the manual." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"Art is the writer not having control, but the subject having control of the writer." ― Paula Vogel</item>
        <item>"The hardest things to write are often the best things to read. And the most deserving to be written." ― David Alejandro Fearnhead</item>
        <item>"Good prose should be transparent, like a window pane." ― George Orwell</item>
        <item>"I think it is vanity to want to put into a story anything but the story itself." ― Julio Cortázar</item>
        <item>"You cannot write unless you write much." ― W. Somerset Maugham</item>
        <item>"Remember that wasted minute at the start of the day? Hard luck but you'll never find it again." ― Cleveland W. Gibson</item>
        <item>"A writing cook and a cooking writer must be bold at the desk as well as the stove." ― M.F.K. Fisher</item>
        <item>"Any fool can write a book and most of them are doing it; but it takes brains to build a house." ― Charles F. Lummis</item>
        <item>"In the country of the story the writer is king." ― Shirley Jackson</item>
        <item>"I edit my own stories to death. They eventually run and hide from me." ― Jeanne Voelker</item>
        <item>"That isn't writing at all, it's typing." ― Truman Capote</item>
        <item>"I'm either going to be a writer or a bum." ― Carl Sandburg</item>
        <item>"It takes writing a billion bad words before you get to the good ones." ― Ray Bradbury</item>
        <item>"That’s the magic of revisions – every cut is necessary, and every cut hurts, but something new always grows." ― Kelly Barnhill</item>
        <item>"As much as I like it when a book I'm writing speeds along, the downside can be that an author becomes too eager to finish and rushes the end. The end is even more important than the first page, and rushing can damage it." ― David Morrell</item>
        <item>"A writer doesn't dream of riches and fame, though those things are nice. A true writer longs to leave behind a piece of themselves, something that withstands the test of time and is passed down for generations." ― C.K. Webb</item>
        <item>"I got this story from someone who had no business in the telling of it." ― Edgar Rice Burroughs</item>
        <item>"As many authors have said, if the writer is not surprised by events, then chances are that the reader will not be either, and grow bored." ― Paul Di Filippo</item>
        <item>"I go silent so I can write. When my tongue is wagging my fingers are silent." ― Sonia Rumzi</item>
        <item>"Biting my truant pen, beating myself for spite: "Fool!" said my muse to me, "look in thy heart, and write." ― Philip Sidney</item>
        <item>"Make no mistake, those who write long books have nothing to say. Of course those who write short books have even less to say." ― Mark Z. Danielewski</item>
        <item>"“I never waited for my Irish Cream coffee to be the right temperature, with a storm happening outside and my fireplace crackling. I wrote every day, at home, in the office, whether I felt like it or not, I just did it." ― Stephen J. Cannell</item>
        <item>"Hold your pen and spare your voice." ― Dorothy Parker</item>
        <item>"We do not wait for inspiration. We work because we've jolly well got to. But when all is said and done, we toil at this particular job because it's turned out to be our particular job, and in a weird sort of way I suppose we may be said to like it." ― Ngaio Marsh</item>
        <item>"The purpose of a writer is to keep civilisation from destroying itself." ― Bernard Malamud</item>
        <item>"If you hear voices, you're a lunatic. If you write down what they say, you're an author." ― Dani Harper</item>
        <item>"An idea, like a ghost, must be spoken to a little before it will explain itself." ― Charles Dickens</item>
        <item>"Goals are dreams with a deadline." ― Napoleon Hill</item>
        <item>"There were no absolutes in fiction, no certain way to deliver what was needed. So it was no surprise most technical writers considered novel-writing a gateway to madness." ― S.A. Reid</item>
        <item>"The best ideas will eat at you for days, maybe even weeks, until something, some incident, some impulse, triggers you to finally express them." ― Criss Jami</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I write about the forest, sometimes I write about the trees, and occasionally I’ll write about the lumberjack. Actually, the lumberjack is more the editing part, figuring what needs to be cut." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"Hard writing makes easy reading." ― Wallace Stegner</item>
        <item>"If you want to write fiction, the best thing you can do is take two aspirins, lie down in a dark room, and wait for the feeling to pass." ― Lawrence Block</item>
        <item>"Sometimes writing everyday is like pulling teeth, painful, but necessary." ― Wendy Swore</item>
        <item>"The only impeccable writers are those who never wrote." ― William Hazlitt</item>
        <item>"Ours is a culture and a time immensely rich in trash as it is in treasures." ― Ray Bradbury</item>
        <item>"A prose that is altogether alive demands something of the reader that the ordinary novel reader is not prepared to give." ― T.S. Eliot</item>
        <item>"Humility is not a virtue in a writer, it is an absolute necessity." ― James Lee Burke</item>
        <item>"It's a very excruciating life facing that blank piece of paper every day and having to reach up somewhere into the clouds and bring something down out of them." ― Truman Capote</item>
        <item>"I write to reach eternity" ― James Jones</item>
        <item>"If you wish to be a writer, write." ― Epictetus</item>
        <item>"It's the writing that teaches you." ― Isaac Asimov</item>
        <item>"Paper is more patient than man." ― Anne Frank</item>
        <item>"To begin impatiently is the worst mistake a writer can make." ― Antony Beevor</item>
        <item>"But what is more to the point is my belief that the habit of writing thus for my own eye only is good practice. It loosens the ligaments. Never mind the misses and the stumbles." ― Virginia Woolf</item>
        <item>"Reading feeds the soul, writing nourishes it!" ― Joanne McClean</item>
        <item>"You know you're writing well when you're throwing good stuff into the wastebasket." ― Ernest Hemingway</item>
        <item>"I don't write stories, I write characters." ― Bhavya Kaushik</item>
        <item>"I'm ambidextrous. I can write just as poorly with either hand." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"Come, let's be calm: no one incapable of restraint was ever a writer." ― Gustave Flaubert</item>
        <item>"I have a pesky little critic in the back of my mind. He's a permanent fixture and passes judgment on everything I write. In order to placate him, especially when I'm endeavoring to write anything as ambitious as a novel, I have to constantly mutter, 'I'm not writing a masterpiece, I'm not writing a masterpiece.' ― Rukhsana Khan</item>
        <item>"Writing is the only art form where a good number of the artists make a slice of their living criticizing one another in print, in public." ― Christian Bauman</item>
        <item>"A novelist is a person who lives in other people's skins." ― E.L. Doctorow</item>
        <item>"Freedom of the press is limited to those who own one." ― A.J. Liebling</item>
        <item>"The reason why so few good books are written is that so few people who can write know anything." ― Walter Bagehot</item>
        <item>"Learn the rules before you break them." ― Steven Taylor Goldsberry</item>
        <item>"Writers write. Everyone else makes excuses." ― Jack M. Bickham</item>
        <item>"Writing is supposed to be difficult, agonizing, a dreadful exercise, a terrible occupation." ― Ray Bradbury</item>
        <item>"I believe the first draft of a book — even a long one — should take no more than three months&#8230; Any longer and — for me, at least — the story begins to take on an odd foreign feel, like a dispatch from the Romanian Department of Public Affairs, or something broadcast on high-band shortwave duiring a period of severe sunspot activity." ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>"Nobody reads a book to get to the middle." ― Mickey Spillane</item>
        <item>"My whole theory of writing I can sum up in one sentence. An author ought to write for the youth of his own generation, the critics of the next, and the schoolmasters of ever afterward." ― F. Scott Fitzgerald</item>
        <item>"I believe one would write better if the climate were bad. If there were a lot of wind and storms for example&#8230;" ― Aldous Huxley</item>
        <item>"Never use abstract nouns when concrete ones will do. If you mean 'More people died' don’t say 'Mortality rose.'" ― C.S. Lewis</item>
        <item>"I write only when inspiration strikes. Fortunately, it strikes every morning at nine o'clock sharp." ― W. Somerset Maugham</item>
        <item>"I found I was repeating myself. It is the beginning of the end when you discover you have style." ― Dashiell Hammett</item>
        <item>"I just rearrange words into a pleasing order for money." ― Terry Pratchett</item>
        <item>"Writer's block, I just drove around it four times. All my favorite writers live there." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"The world requires me to re-write its wretched dialogue!" ― Richard Greenberg</item>
        <item>"Writers are always anxious, always on the run - from the telephone, from responsibilities, from the distractions of the world." ― Edna O\'Brien</item>
        <item>"As for my next book, I won't write it till it has grown heavy in my mind like a ripe pear; pendant, gravid, asking to be cut or it will fall." ― Virginia Woolf</item>
        <item>"Writing is the supreme solace." ― W. Somerset Maugham</item>
        <item>"My circumstances of unrelieved responsibility and permanent distraction necessitated the short story form." ― Raymond Carver</item>
        <item>"Assuming you can write clear English sentences, give up all worry about communication. If you want to communicate, use the telephone." ― Richard Hugo</item>
        <item>"You want to tell a story? Grow a heart. Grow two. Now, with the second heart, smash the first one into bits." ― Charles Yu</item>
        <item>"The best writing is rewriting." ― E.B. White</item>
        <item>I suggested to her that she start writing. "I can't write at all," she said. "Neither can many bestsellers," I replied. "But that pesky detail didn't stop them." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"If I didn't know the ending of a story, I wouldn't begin. I always write my last lines, my last paragraph first, and then I go back and work towards it. I know where I'm going. I know what my goal is. And how I get there is God's grace." ― Katherine Anne Porter</item>
        <item>"Arrogance kills creativity." ― A.M. Riley</item>
        <item>"You've got to be smart enough to write and stupid enough not to think about all the things that might go wrong." ― Sarah Gilbert</item>
        <item>"To be a writer is to embrace rejection as a way of life." ― Dana Stabenow</item>
        <item>"All writers have this vague hope that the elves will come in the night and finish any stories." ― Neil Gaiman</item>
        <item>"If a book is well written, I always find it too short." ― Jane Austen</item>
        <item>"We have this idea that we need to be in the mood to write. We don't." ― Julia Cameron</item>
        <item>"The greatest part of a writer's time is spent in reading, in order to write: a man will turn over half a library to make one book." ― Samuel Johnson</item>
        <item>"Writing saved me from the sin and inconvenience of violence." ― Alice Walker</item>
        <item>"One day, I shall explode like an artillery shell and all my bits will be found on the writing table." ― Gustave Flaubert</item>
        <item>"It begins with a character, usually, and once he stands up on his feet and begins to move, all I can do is trot along behind him with a paper and pencil trying to keep up long enough to put down what he says and does." ― William Faulkner</item>
        <item>"I write and that way rid myself of me and then at last I can rest." ― Clarice Lispector</item>
        <item>"Writing is a solitary business. It takes over your life. In some sense, a writer has no life of his own. Even when he's there, he’s not really there." ― Paul Auster</item>
        <item>"I don't write fantasy; I write historical novels about an imaginary place." ― Raymond E. Feist</item>
        <item>"Only half the story is true. The rest is necessary." ― John Yau</item>
        <item>"When my horse is running good, I don't stop to give him sugar." ― William Faulkner</item>
        <item>"Writing doesn’t get easier with experience. The more you know, the harder it is to write." ― Tim O\'Brien</item>
        <item>"The writer's life: Hard days, lots of work, no money, too much silence. Nobody's fault. You chose it." ― Bill Barich</item>
        <item>"In writing a novel, when in doubt, have two guys come through the door with guns." ― Raymond Chandler</item>
        <item>"If a person is not talented enough to be a novelist, not smart enough to be a lawyer, and his hands are too shaky to perform operations, he becomes a journalist." ― Norman Mailer</item>
        <item>"Writing is the emotional morphine." ― Mariam Maarouf</item>
        <item>"It's doubtful that anyone with an internet connection at his workplace is writing good fiction." ― Jonathan Franzen</item>
        <item>"I wisely started with a map." ― J.R.R. Tolkien</item>
        <item>"Loafing is the most productive part of a writer's life." ― James Norman Hall</item>
        <item>"Most writers might as well write in invisible ink, because if what they're writing is forgettable, it might as well be invisible too." ― Jarod Kintz</item>
        <item>"Words have weight." ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>"Of all human activities, writing is the one for which it is easiest to find excuses not to begin – the desk's too big, the desk's too small, there's too much noise, there's too much quiet, it's too hot, too cold, too early, too late&#8230; ― Robert Harris</item>
        <item>If I ever saw my muse she would be an old woman with a tight bun and spectacles poking me in the middle of the back and growling, "Wake up and write the book!" ― Kerry Greenwood</item>
        <item>"As an experienced editor, I disapprove of flashbacks, foreshadowings, and tricksy devices; they belong in the 1980s with M.A.s in postmodernism and chaos theory." ― David Mitchell</item>
        <item>"A cliche is everything you've ever heard of." ― Janet Fitch</item>
        <item>"People who understand everything get no stories." ― Bertolt Brecht</item>
        <item>"The pen is mightier than the sword unless it's a real sword in which case the guy with the pen should run away fast." ― Roger Eschbacher</item>
        <item>Write. Write more. Write even more. Write even more than that. Write when you don\'t want to. Write when you do. Write when you have something to say. Write when you don\'t. Write every day. Keep writing." ― Brian Clark</item>
        <item>"Reading maketh a full man; conference a ready man; and writing an exact man." ― Francis Bacon</item>
        <item>"The story I am writing exists, written in absolutely perfect fashion, some place, in the air. All I must do is find it, and copy it." ― Jules Renard</item>
        <item>"Writing in English is like throwing mud at a wall." ― Joseph Conrad</item>
        <item>"All the stories I would like to write persecute me. When I am in my chamber, it seems as if they are all around me, like little devils, and while one tugs at my ear, another tweaks my nose, and each says to me, 'Sir, write me, I am beautiful.'" ― Umberto Eco</item>
        <item>"When writing goes painfully, when it's hideously difficult, and one feels real despair (ah, the despair, silly as it is, is real!)–then naturally one ought to continue with the work; it would be cowardly to retreat." ― Joyce Carol Oates</item>
        <item>"You can't put much on paper before you betray your secret self, try as you will to keep things civil." ― Patricia Hampl</item>
        <item>"If the storytellers told it true, all stories would end in death." ― George Pelecanos</item>
        <item>"Never put off writing until you are better at it." ― Gary Henderson</item>
        <item>"Writing feels safer somehow. I can catch myself before I say the wrong thing." ― Hillary Frank</item>
        <item>"In the glad old days, before the rise of modern morbidities&#8230; it used to be thought a disadvantage to be misunderstood." ― G.K. Chesterton</item>
        <item>"Talent is extremely common. What is rare is the willingness to endure the life of the writer." ― Kurt Vonnegut</item>
        <item>"I speak to the Black experience, but I am always talking about the human condition - about what we can endure, dream, fail at and survive." ― Maya Angelou</item>
        <item>"I don't go back and look at my early work, because the last time I did, many years ago, it left me cringing. If one publishes, then one is creating a public record of Learning to Write." ― Lorrie Moore</item>
        <item>"In displaying the psychology of your characters, minute particulars are essential. God save us from vague generalizations!" ― Anton Chekhov</item>
        <item>"Anyone who says writing is easy isn't doing it right." ― Amy Joy</item>
        <item>"Aha! Today I shall become an author! And I will auth and auth and auth and make a squillion dollars, whoopee!" ― Brian Jacques</item>
        <item>"You can't judge a book by it's cover but you can sure sell a bunch of books if you have a good one." ― Jayce O\'Neal</item>
        <item>"It's often a matter of sitting in front of the computer and worrying. It's what writing comes down to - worrying that things aren't going to work out." ― Khaled Hosseini</item>
        <item>"If you're silent for a long time, people just arrive in your mind." ― Alice Walker</item>
        <item>"If you have not done things worthy of being written about, at least write things worthy of being read." ― Giacomo Casanova</item>
        <item>"Writer's block is just a symptom of feeling like you have nothing to say, combined with the rather weird idea that you should feel the need to say something. Why? If you have something to say, then say it. If not, enjoy the silence while it lasts. The noise will return soon enough." ― Hugh MacLeod</item>
        <item>"Just tell the truth, and they'll accuse you of writing black humor." ― Charles Willeford</item>
        <item>"As with all other aspects of the narrative art, you will improve with practice, but practice will never make you perfect. Why should it? What fun would that be?" ― Stephen King</item>
        <item>"If I could sum it up in 50 words, I wouldn't have needed to write a whole novel about it." ― Patrick Rothfuss</item>
        <item>"I am a writer perhaps because I am not a talker." ― Gwendolyn Brook</item>
        <item>"This is no book. Whoever touches this touches a man." ― Ezra Pound</item>
        <item>"Everyone in the South has no time for reading because they are all too busy writing." ― William Faulkner</item>
        <item>"When you write about what you dream, you become a writer. When you dream about what you write, you become haunted by a curse." ― A. Saleh</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>